{"words": [
  {
  "id":1,
  "question": "Ravage",
  "answer" : 0,
  "option" : [
		"To Devastate",
		"To acquire",
		"To hurt someone unintentionally"
	],
  "hint" : "Fears that a war could ravage their country",
	"selected": null

},
  {
  "id":2,
  "question": "Ostracize",
  "answer" : 2,
  "option" : [
    "Being obstacle for someone",
		"To influence",
		"Exclude from a society or group."
		
	],
  "hint" : "A group of people were ostracized, and persecuted for centuries",
	"selected": null

},
{
  "id":3,
  "question": "Ravenous",
  "answer" : 1,
  "option" : [
    "Self Dependent",
		"Voracious",
		"A ray of hope"
		
	],
  "hint" : "I'd been out all day and was ravenous",
	"selected": null

},
{
  "id":4,
  "question": "Subdue",
  "answer" : 1,
  "option" : [
    "To become Happy",
		"Vanquish",
		"Thinking Positive"
		
	],
  "hint" : "He managed to subdue an instinct to applaud",
	"selected": null

},
{
  "id":5,
  "question": "Spry",
  "answer" : 0,
  "option" : [
    "Active",
		"Looking for Opportunities",
		"Manifesting"
		
	],
  "hint" : "He continued to look spry into his eighties",
	"selected": null

},
{
  "id":6,
  "question": "Protege",
  "answer" : 0,
  "option" : [
    "A person who is guided and supported by experienced person",
		"Looking for Guidance",
		"Influential person."
		
	],
  "hint" : "Lake, a Trump protege, accuses elections officials of slow-rolling returns",
	"selected": null

},
{
  "id":7,
  "question": "Precipitate",
  "answer" : 1,
  "option" : [
    "A maintain distance",
		"To cause",
		"To perform well"
		
	],
  "hint" : "The incident precipitated a political crisis",
	"selected": null

},
{
  "id":8,
  "question": "Fervid",
  "answer" : 2,
  "option" : [
    "A lazy person",
		"To accelerate",
		"Passionate"
		
	],
  "hint" : "A letter of fervid thanks",
	"selected": null

},
{
  "id":9,
  "question": "Caseous",
  "answer" : 0,
  "option" : [
    "Cheeselike",
		"To be alert",
		"Good Minded"
		
	],
  "hint" : "Surgical intervention was performed to excise the caseous lesions",
	"selected": null

},
{
  "id":10,
  "question": "Acrophobia",
  "answer" : 0,
  "option" : [
    "Having Danger",
		"To be calm",
		"Fear of heights."
		
	],
  "hint" : "Because I have acrophobia, I never ride anything other than the Ferris wheel at the amusement park",
	"selected": null

}


]}